Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Peter P. Carr Papers
0
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.055
60 Linear Feet
- Series I: American Options, 1965-2002; 60 Linear Feet
  - An Exact Analytic Formula for the Value of an American Put Option on a Non-Dividend-Paying Stock, 1994-08-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography on American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Derivatives - A Review; Aase; 1997, 1997-12-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - On Trading American Options; Ahn and Wilmott; OCIAM, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Optimal Stopping and Weak Convergence Methods for some Problems in Financial Economics; Ait-Sahlia, F., 1995-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Corrected Random Walk Approximations for Contingent Claims Problems; Ait-Sahlia, F; Stanford University, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Approximations for American Options; Ait-Sahlia and Lai, 1995-12-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jumping in Line; Albanese, Jaimungal, and Rubisov; July 2000, 2000-07-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pricing American Options in a Term Structure Economy; Amin, Kaushik; Cornell WP 1988, 1988-11-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Discrete-Time Valuation of American Optics with Stochastic Interest Rates; Amin, K.I. Bodurtha, J.N.; University of Michigan, 1993-07-1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Convergence of American Option Values from Discrete to Continuous Time Financial Models; Amin/Khanna 4/92, 1992-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Primal-Dual Simulation Algorithm for Pricing Multi-Dimensional American Options; Andersen and Broadie; July 2001, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pricing American Options Using Monte Carlo Simulation; Averbukh, V.; Cornell U WP 97, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A Method for Computing Double Band Policies for Switching Between Two Diffusions; Avram, F., 1996-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Analytic Representations and Approximations to American Option Pricing; Balakrishna, B.S.; UC Boulder WP, 1996-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Critical Stock Price Near Expiration; Barles, Burdeau, Romano, and Samsoen; Math Fin Apr 1995, 1995-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Convergence of Numerical Schemes for Parabolic Equations Arising in Finance Theory; Barles, G.; Newton Institute - Cambridge, 1995-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Path-Dependent Options; Barone-Adesi, Giovanni, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Free Boundary of American Puts; Barone-Adesi, Giovanni; 4/9/92, 1992-04-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Free Boundary Problems in the Valuation of Securities; Baron-Adesi; 11/89, 1989-11-14-1990-04-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Path-Dependent Options; G. Barone-Adesi and M. Chesney, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Approximations for the Values of American Options; Barone-Adesi/Elliot, 1989-10-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Valuation of American Options; Barone-Adesi and Elliot; Univ of Alberta 89, 1989-10-05-1990-08-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Efficient Analytic Approximation of American Option Values; Baron-Adesi/Whaley JF; 1987, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - On the Valuation of American Put Options on Dividend-Paying Stocks; Barone-Adesi and Whaley, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Numerical Valuation of High Dimensional Multivariate American Securities; Digital Equip. Corp; J. Barraquand and D. Martineau; April 1994, 1994-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Optimal Exercise Boundary of American Options; Basso, Nardon, and Pianca; Mar 2002, 2002-03-2002-04-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - An Analysis of the Effects of Continuous Dividends on the Exercise of American Options; Basso, Nardon, and Pianca; Venice WP 02, 2002-07-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Discrete and Continuous Time Approximations of the Optimal Exercise Boundary of American Options; Basso, Nardon, and Pianca, 2002-03-25; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jumps and Stochastic Volatility: Exchange Rate Processes Implicit in Deutsche Mark Options; Bates, D.; RFS 96, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - A New Look at Optimal Stopping Problems Related, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Closed-Form Approximation of American Options; Bjerksund and Stensland; Scand. J. Mgmt 93, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Pricing of Options and Corporate Liabilities; Black/Scholes JPE, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Probability of Early Exercise: Foreign Currency Options and Foreign Currency Futures Options; Bodurtha, Courtadon; 1/93, 1993-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Simulation Estimators of Optimal Early Exercise; Bossaerts, Peter; 1989, 1989-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Pricing of the American Put Under Levy Processes; Beyarchenko, S; U Penn 02, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Options: A Monte Carlo Approach; Boyle, Phelim; JFE; 1977, 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Accelerated Binomial Option Pricing Model; Green, Richard, 1991-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Valuation of American Put Options; Brennan & Schwartz, 1977-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Finite Difference Methods and Jump Processes Arising in the Pricing of Contingent Claims: A Synthesis; Brennan/Schwartz, 1978; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Pricing American Options: Managing Risk with Early Exercise; Brill/Harriff, 1986; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Valuation of American Options on Multiple Assets; Broadie & Detemple, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - American Capped Call Options on Dividend-Paying Assets; Broadie, M. and Detemple, J., 1993-1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - American Options on Dividend-Paying Assets; Broadie & Detemple, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - American Option Valuation: New Bonds, Approximations, and a Comparison of Existing Methods; Broadie, M. and Detemple, J., 1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Nonparametric Estimation of American Options Exercise Boundaries and Call Prices; Broadie, Detemple, Ghysels, & Torres, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - American Options with Stochastic Dividends and Volatility: A Nonparametric Investigation; Broadie, Detemple, Ghysels & Torres, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Pricing American-Style Securities Using Simulation; Broadie & Glasserman, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - A Stochastic Mesh Method for Pricing High-Dimensional American Options; Broader & Glasserman, 1997-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Monte Carlo Methods for Pricing High-Dimensional American Options: An Overview; Broader & Glasserman, 1997-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - A Simple and Numerically Efficient Method for American Puts Using a Modified Geske-Johnson Approach; Bunch, D.S. & Johnson, H., 1992-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - The American Put Option and Its Critical Stock Price; Bunch & Johnson, 2000-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - On the Pricing of American Options When the Asset Follows a Mean-Reverting Process; Cadenillas, Elliott, & Leger, 2002-06-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Beyond the American Put; Carr, Elliott, Geman, & Madan, 1997-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Evaluation of American Option Prices in a Path Integral Framework Using Fourier-Hermite Series Expansions; Chiarella, El-Hassan & Kucera, 1997-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Premature Exercise and American Put Evaluation; Chesney & Lefoll, 1993-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - American Options: Theory and Numerical Analysis; Carverhill/Webber, 1988-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Richardson Extrapolation Techniques for Pricing American-style Options; Chang, Chung, & Stapleton, 2001-05-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Linear Complementarity and the American Put - A GAMS/PATH Implementation; Chan, S., 1998-09-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Analytical Upper Bounds for American Option Prices; Chen & Yeh, 1999-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Pricing American Currency Options: An Analytical Approach; Chesney, Marc, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Analytical Solutions to the Pricing of American Bond and Yield Options; Chesney, Elliott, Gibson, 1991-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - M. Chesney & R. Gibson, State Space Symmetry and Two Factor Option Pricing Models; IGBF IBFM #9402; 1993, 1993-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Clarke & Parrott; The Multigrid Solution of Two-factor American Put Options, 1996-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Efficient Monte Carlo Valuation and Hedging of Contingent Claims; Clewlow/Carverhill, 1992-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - The Wise, For Cure, on Exercise Depend; Cornwall/Price; Risk Magazine, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - A More Accurate Finite Difference Approximation for the Valuation of Options; Courtadon, G.; JFQA, 1982-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Options Markets; Cox & Rubinstein, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Accelerating American Option Pricing in Lattices; Curran, M., 1994-12-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - American Options and Transaction Fees; Davis, M.H.A. & Zariphopoulou, T., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - On the Optimal Stopping Problems for One-Dimensional Diffusions with Random Discounting; Dayanik, Savas, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - On the Optimal Stopping Problem for One-Dimensional Diffusions; Dayanik, S. & Karatzas, I., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - A Variational Approach for Pricing Options and Corporate Bonds; Decamps, J.P. & Rochet, J.C., 1993-07-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - The Ratio of American & European Put Options When Time to Maturity is Small; Delbaen, F., 2000-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Fast Numerical Valuation of American, Exotic and Complex Options; Applied Mathematical Finance; Dempster & Hutton, 1997-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Pricing American Stock Options by Linear Programming; Dempster & Hutton, 1999-08-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Pricing Exotic American Options Fitting the Volatility Smile; Dempster & Richards, 1999-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - The Valuation of American Options on the Minimum of Two Dividend-Paying Assets; Detemple, Feng, & Tian, 2001-02-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - The Valuation of American Options for a Class of Diffusion Processes; Detemple & Tian, 2002-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Some Mathematical Results in the Pricing of American Options; Euro. Journal of Applied Mathematics 4; Dewynne, J. N. & Howison, S.D., 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - American Option Pricing under GARCH by a Markov Chain Approximation; Duan & Simonato, 1997-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - The Optimal Stopping Problem for a General American Put-Option; Karoui, N.E. & Karatzas, I., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - American Options with Dividends Near Expiry; Evans, Kuske, & Keller, 2000-08-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - An Explicit Formula for American Puts; Firoozye, N., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Analytic Approximation for the Valuation of American Put Options on Stocks with Known Dividends; Fischer, E.O., 1990-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - "Estimating Implied PDFs from American Options: A New Semi-Parametric Approach"; Flamouris, D.V. & Giamouridis, D.G., 2000-10-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Quadratic Convergence of a Penalty Method for Valuing American Options; Forsyth & Vetzal, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Valuation by Approximation: A Comparison of Alternative Option Valuation Techniques; Geske & Shastri, 1985-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - An Improved Analytic Approximation for American Option Pricing; Gandhi, Kooros, & Salkin, 1993-03-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - "A Monte Carlo Method for Pricing American Options"; Garcia, D., 1999-08-1999-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - A Monte Carlo Method for Pricing American Options, 2000-08-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Semper Tempus Fugit; Risk Magazine; Garman, M., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - An Analytical Approach to the Valuation of American Path-Dependent Options; Gao, Huang, & Subrahmanyam, 1996-07-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Martingale Approach to Pricing Perpetual American Options on Two Stocks; Gerber & Shiu, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - The Valuation of Compound Options; JFE; Geske, R., 1979; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - The American Put Option Valued Analytically; Geske and Johnson; JF Dec 84, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Early Exercise of American Puts; Geske, Robert and Shastri, Kuldeep; July 1981, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Estimating the Early Exercise Boundary and Pricing American Options; Goldenberg and Schmidt, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - On the Early Exercise Boundary of the American Put Option; Goodman and Ostrov; Aug 2000, 2000-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Path-Dependent Options: Extending the Monte Carlo Simulation Approach; Working Paper, 1993-11-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Simulation and the Early-Exercise Option Problem; Grant, Vora and Weeks; JFE, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Efficient Numerical Methods for Pricing American Options; Gukhal, Chandrasekhar; WP Nov 96, 1996-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Analytical Valuation of American Options on Jump-Diffusion Processes; Gukhal, Reddy; Columbia WP 96, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A General Approach to the Analytical Valuation of American Options; Gukhal, C.; Nov 2001, 2001-11-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Closed-Form Solutions for Perpetual American Put Options with Regime Switching; Guo and Zhang, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Exercise by Numbers; Guth, Michael 2/92, 1992-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Multinomial Approximating Models for Options with k State Variables"; Kamrad/Ritchken, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Optimization Problems in the Theory of Continuous Trading; Karatzas, Ioannis, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - On the Pricing of American Options; Karatzas, Ioannis; Appl Math Optim 1988, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Valuing and Hedging American Put Options Using Neural Networks; Kelly, D.; CMU WP 94, 1994-12-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Valuation of American Options via Penalty Methods; Khaliq, Voss and Kazmi, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Analytic Valuation of American Options on Futures Contracts; Kim, In Joon; 1989, 1989-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Analytic Valuation of American Options; Kim, In Joon; WP S-90-15, 1989-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Analytic Approximation of the Optimal Exercise Boundaries for American Futures Options; Kim, J., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Analytic Valuation of American Options; Kim, J.; Rev. Fin. Stud. 1990, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Predicting Early Exercise Premia in American Put Prices; Kim, Hongshik, 1994-09-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - A Simplified Approach to the Valuation of American Options and its Applications; Kim, Yu 2/93, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Optimal Exercise Boundary for an American Put Option; Kuske and Keller; Applied Math Fin 98, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - A Remark on American Securities; Kusuoka, S., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Error Estimates for the Binomial Approximation of American Put Options; Lamberton, D.; Annals of Applied Prob 1998, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Convergence of the Critical Price in the Approximation of American Options; Lamberton, Damien 4/93, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Brownian Optimal Stopping and Random Walks; Lamberton, D., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Course on American Options; Laurence, Peter, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bounds for the Price of an American Option on Several Assets: Index and Spread Options; Laurence, P., 2001-03-11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Introduction to the Valuation of American Options: Qualitative Properties; Laurence, Peter, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bounds for the price of an American option on several assets: Index and Spread options; Laurence, Peter, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Random-Time Binomial Model; Leisen, D.P.J., 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Series Solution to the Critical Stock Price; Lewis, Alan, 1995-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Early Exercise Boundary for the American Put-Option as the Solution of a Volterra Equation; Little, T., 1998-02-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - A New Integral Representation of the Early Exercise Boundary for American Put Options; Little, Pant & Hou, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Valuing American Options by Simulation: A Simple Least-Squares Approach; Longstaff & Schwartz, 1998-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Analytical Valuation of American-style Asian Options; Hansen & Jorgensen, 1997-11-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Dual American Option Pricing; Hansen & Mussavian, 1997-12-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Accelerating the Crank-Nicolson Method in American Option Pricing; Hansen & Osterby, 1998-04-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Pricing American Options Under Variance Gamma; Hirsa & Madan, 2001-08-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - A Simple Technique for the Valuation and Hedging of American Options; Ho, Stapleton & Subrahmanyam, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - A Valuation of American Options with Stochastic Interest Rates: A Generalization of the Geske-Johnson Technique; Ho, Stapleton & Subrahmanyam, 1996-09-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Valuation of American Options; Hoffmann, C., 2000-10-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - An MPEC Approach to Inverse Pricing of American Options: The Case of an Implied Volatility Surface; Huang & Pang, 1999-11-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Pricing American Options with Transaction Costs by Complementarity Methods; Huang & Pang, 1999-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Option Pricing and Linear Complimentarity; Huang & Pang, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Monte-Carlo Valuation of American Options Through Computation of the Optimal Exercise Frontier; Ibanez & Zapatero, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Valuation of Contingent Claims with Multiple Earlier Exercise Opportunities; Ibanez, A., 2000-04-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Approximating American Options and Other Financial Contracts Using "Barrier" Derivatives; Ingersoll, Jonathan E. Jr., 1997-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Optimal Stopping and the American Put; Jacka, S.D., 1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - An Efficient and General Method to Value American-style Equity and FX Options in the Prescence of User-Defined Smiles and Time-Dependent Volatility; Jackel & Rebonato, 2000-03-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Variational Inequalities and the Pricing of American Options; Jaillet, Lamberton & Lapeyre, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Formulas for American Options; Jamshidian, Farshid, 1989-1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - An Analysis of American Options; Jamshidian, Farshid, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - An Analytic Approximation for the American Put Price; Johnson, H.E., 1983; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - American Bond Option Pricing in One-Factor Dynamic Term Structure Models; Jorgensen, P.L., 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - American Option Pricing; Jorgensen, P., 1994-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Fast, Accurate and Inelegant Valuation of American Options; Joubert & Rogers, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Yet Another Approximation of the American Put; Jourdain & Martini, 1999-12-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - American Prices Embedded in European Prices; Jourdan & Martini, 1999-11-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Pricing an American Option by Approximating Its Early Exercise Boundary As a Multi-Piece Exponential Function; Ju, Nengjiu, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - An Efficient and Reliable Approximate Formula for Pricing American Options; Ju, Nengjiu, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - An Approximate Formula for Pricing American Options; Ju & Zhong, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Analytic Approximation for the American Put Option; MacMillan, L.W., 1986; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Successive Over Relaxation Method for American Options; Maini & Fernandes, 1995-03-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - A Fully Explicit Analytic Approximation Formula for Pricing American Options; Mane, S.R., 1999-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - The Early Exercise Boundary of American Options near Expiry; Mane, S.R., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Asymptotic Behavior of Early Exercise Boundary; Mane, S., 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - A Put-Call Symmetric Analytic Approximation Formula for Pricing American Options; Mane, S.R., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - A Pricing Model for American Options with Stochastic Interest Rates; Menkveld & Vorst; Erasmus U., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - On the Approximation of Optimal Stopping Problems with Application to Financial Mathematics; Marcozzi, M.; UNLV WP 99, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - The Numerical Analysis of Certain Free Boundary Problems Arising in Financial Economics; Mason, Scott, 1977-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - An Integro-Differential Parabolic Variational Inequality Connected with the Problem of the American Option Pricing; Mastroeni and Matzeu; Zeit, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - A Parity Result for American Options; McDonald and Schroder, 1990-11-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - The Early Exercise Premium in American Option Prices Direct Empirical Evidence; McMurray/Yadav, 1993-06-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Theory of Rational Option Pricing; Merton, Robert, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Front Tracking of Free Boundaries with Curvature Terms; Meyer, Gunter H., 1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - The Numerical Valuation of Options with Underlying Jumps; Meyer, G.; Acta Math. Univ. Com., 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - The Evaluation of American Options with the Method of Lines; Meyer and van der Hoek, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - The Pricing of the American Option; Myneni, Ravi; Stanford WP, 1990-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - The Pricing of the American Option; Myneni, Ravi, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - The Optimal Exercise Boundary and the American Equity Put; Myneni, Ravi, 1989-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - The Pricing of the American Option; Myneni, Ravi; Stanford WP, 1990-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - "Pricing American and Bermudan Interest Rate Options in the Market Models"; Noubir, M.; Credit Lyonnais-Risk Conferences, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 84)